What is it about me? Do I not look fun enough?
我是哪裡不對？ 我看起來不夠有趣嗎？
Is there something repellent about me?
我是有哪裡討人厭嗎？
How was the party?
派對好玩嗎？
It couldn't have been worse. A woman literally passed through me.
難玩死了 有個女人對我大送秋波
What is it? Am I hideously unattractive?
我有那麼不討人喜歡嗎？
No,you are not. You are very attractive.
不，才怪
I go through the same thing.
我也是一樣
When I put on a little weight, I question everything.
每當我增加了一點點重量 我就開始質疑一切了
I've put on weight?
你說我變胖了？
Did you want to...?
你要…？
No,not weight. More like insulation.
不是，不是重量 說絕緣體比較恰當
I'm unemployed, in dire need of a project.
錢德，我正在失業 迫切需要做點事情
Wanna work out? I can remake you.
你要不要運動？我可以重塑你
I would,but that might get in the way of my lying-around time.
我很想，但那或許會妨礙 我那些無所事事的時間
Please?
拜託啦
Come on,let her do it!
對啦，讓她做一下嘛
All right.
好吧…
If we put on spandex and my boobs are bigger than yours,I'm going home.
但我穿上緊身衣後 胸部比你大的話，我就不來了
Your boobs are fine.
你的胸部很好呀
I shouldn't have said anything.
聽著，我們不該亂開烏鴉嘴的
Come here. Come here!
過來…
Can't make hands meet!
雙手都合不起來了
The One Where Ross Finds Out
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河馬壓縮製作 本字幕為河馬根據R3DVD OCR得來
六人行 第2季 第07集 羅斯發現瑞秋對他有意思
Let's do it!
好，開始吧
What?
怎麼了？
Nothing. Just never seen your little stretchy pants before.
沒什麼 只是沒看過你穿緊身褲而已呀
And we're changing.
我去換衣服
Come on,give me five more!
加油，再做五個
Five more!
再五個
Five more and I'll flash you.
做就給你看波波
One...
一…
...two...
…二…
...two and a half.
…二點五
Just show me one of them.
好了，給我看一邊吧
中央公園
She's insane!
她瘋了
The woman is insane.
那個女人瘋了
It's before work,after work, and during work.
上班前，上班後，上班中
She's got me doing butt-clenches at my desk.
她叫我在公司做收臀運動
And now they won't bring me my mail anymore.
現在，他們不再送郵件給我了
Hey,Pheebs. How'd it go with Scott?
菲菲，你昨晚跟史考怎麼樣？
It was nice. Took him to a romantic restaurant...
不錯呀 帶他去一家浪漫的餐廳…
...ordered champagne. Nice.
…點了香檳，很好
He still won't put out?
那個傢伙還是不行動啊？
Nope. Zilch. Nothing.
不，零蛋，沒有
Sorry,Pheebs.
真遺憾，菲菲
Look,I don't mind taking it slow.
我不在乎慢慢的來
I like him a lot.
我很喜歡他
He's really interesting, and he's really sweet.
他這個人很有趣，人也很甜
Why won't he give it up?
他幹嘛那麼矜持呢？
Maybe he drives his car on the other side of the road.
或許他跟我們反方向開車
If you know what I mean.
你懂我的意思吧？
No. What do you mean? He's not British.
不懂，他又不是英國人
Maybe he's gay.
他或許是同性戀
I don't think that's the problem.
不，我覺得問題不在那兒
We went dancing the other night...
因為我們前幾天去跳舞…
...and just the way he held me so close and looked into my eyes....
…他緊緊抱住我的那個樣子 還有他凝視我眼睛的樣子…
I just definitely felt something.
我覺得他對我絕對有意思
But how much can you tell from a look?
是啊，從眼神能看出多少呢？
I felt it on my hip. I could tell.
不，我是從屁股感覺到的
Yo,Bing! Racquetball in 20 minutes.
錢兄弟，二十分鐘後打壁球
Joey,be a pal. Lift up my hand and smack her with it.
喬伊，好兄弟 舉起我的手賞她一巴掌
Oh,Rachel! Don't look.
瑞秋，你別看
What?
什麼？
I don't care. I have a date tonight.
我才不在乎 我今晚有約會
You have a date?
你有約會？
Monica's setting me up.
對呀，摩妮卡介紹的
What about Ross and....
那羅斯跟…
What? My whole insane jealousy thing?
我打翻醋罈子那碼子事啊？
Well,you know, as much fun as that was...
雖然那還挺有趣的…
... I've decided to opt for sanity.
…我決定不再瘋下去了
You're okay about all this?
你真的不介意那些了？
Oh,yeah,come on! I'm moving on.
少來了，我還要過我的日子呢
He can press her up against that window as much as he wants.
他愛怎麼把她壓在那扇窗子上 就怎麼壓吧
For all I care,he can throw her through the damn thing.
乾脆把她摔過窗子算了
Hi,guys.
各位
Monica,I'll come by tomorrow and pick up Fluffy's old cat toys,okay?
摩妮卡，我想明天早上過來 拿膨脹以前的貓玩具
If you say his full name.
不講全名就不給喔
Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toys?
好吧，那我明天可不可以 過來拿喵喵膨膨的貓玩具？
All right.
沒問題
-You're getting a cat? -Actually,we're getting a cat.
你要養貓啊？ 事實上，是我們要養貓
Together?
一起養？
Both of you? Together?
你們兩個？一起？
It'll live with Ross half the time and with me half the time.
我們想它會一半時間跟羅斯住 一半跟我住
Well,isn't that just lovely?
那是不是很棒呢
That's something you'll enjoy...
那是一件你們兩個…
...for a really,really, really long time.
…可以疼愛非常非常久的東西
Hopefully.
希望如此
Look at that. I gotta go! I got a date!
我得走了 我有約會
With a man.
跟個男人喔
You guys have a really good night...
祝各位今晚順利…
...and you two have a really good cat.
…而你們兩個得到一隻好貓
We're not supposed to take these when we leave.
順手牽羊是不對的
I don't know if Monica told you,but this my first date since my divorce.
我不曉得摩妮卡有沒有告訴你 這是我離婚之後的第一次約會
If I seem a little nervous...
我顯得有一點緊張…
... I am.
…那是真的
How long do cats live?
貓能活多久啊？
I'm sorry?
你說什麼？
Cats. How long do they live?
貓，貓能活多久？
Figuring you don't throw them under a bus or something?
如果不把它們丟到 巴士下面去送死的話
Maybe 1 5,1 6 years.
大概是十五，六年吧
Well,that's just great.
那真是太棒了
Cheers!
乾杯
Right. Clink.
好，乾杯
Monica told you I was cuter than this,didn't she?
摩妮卡把我吹得比本人可愛 對不對？
No,Michael,it's not you. Sorry. It's just....
不，麥克 不是因為你…
It's this thing.
我是…我另外有心事
It's not as bad as it sounds...
事情說不定沒那麼糟啦…
... but this friend of mine is getting a cat with his girlfriend.
…我有一個朋友 他跟他的女朋友要養貓
Oh,that does sound....
聽起來的確是…
He just started going out with her.
他們兩個才剛剛開始交往不久
Is this guy an old boyfriend?
他是你以前的男朋友嗎？
Yeah,he wishes.
他想得美喔
I'm sorry. Look at me.
對不起，你瞧瞧我
Michael,let's talk about you.
好了，麥克，談談你吧
So....
那麼…
Did you ever get a pet with a girlfriend?
以前你跟女朋友 一起養過寵物嗎？
-So I figured it out. -What?
我知道為什麼了 什麼？
Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me.
史考為什麼不想跟我上床
I'm not sexy enough.
因為我不夠性感
Phoebe,that's crazy.
菲比，別傻了
When I first met you, you know what I said?
第一次看到你之後 你知道我對錢德說什麼嗎？
I said,"Excellent butt,great rack."
我說「前突後翹，有看頭」
Really? That's so sweet.
真的？嘴好甜
I mean,I'm officially offended. But that's so sweet.
說實在的，我被冒犯了 可是感覺真好
If you wanna know what the deal is, you're gonna have to ask him.
菲菲，你想知道為什麼的話 你必須開口去問他
You're right. You're right.
你說得對…
You are so "yum"!
你真棒耶
I mean,it's a cat,you know? It's a cat.
那是隻貓 你知道的，貓
Why can't they get a bug? One of those fruit flies.
他們幹嘛不養只昆蟲 養只果蠅就好了
Those things that live for a day.
那種只活一，兩天的東西
What are they called?
它們叫什麼？
Fruit flies?
果蠅？
Thank you.
謝謝
Would you like dessert?
要不要點甜點啊？
No dessert.
不，不要了
Just the check. Please.
我想結賬
Oh,no. You're not having fun,are you?
你玩得不開心？
No,no,I am.
不…我很開心
But only because I've been playing the movie Diner in my head.
不過剛才那一個半小時 我都在回憶「餐館」的情節
Oh,look at me.
你看我
Look at me.
I'm on a date with a really great guy.
我在跟一個很棒的男人約會
All I can think about is Ross...
卻滿腦子是羅斯…
...and his cat...
…跟他的貓…
...and his Julie.
…還有他的茱莉
I just want to get over him. Why can't I do that?
我只是想忘了他 天啊，為什麼我不能呢？
Look,I've been through a divorce. Trust me,you're gonna be fine.
聽我說，我經歷過離婚 相信我，不會有事的
You can't see it because you haven't had closure
你還看不出來 因為你跟他還沒有了結嘛…
Closure!
了結！
That's what it is! That's what I need!
就是那個，我就需要那個
God,you're brilliant!
天啊，你太棒了
Why didn't I think of that? How do I get that?
我為什麼沒有想到？ 我要怎麼了結？
Well,there's no one way really,it's just....
這沒有一定的方法，這只是…
Whatever it takes so that you can finally say to him:
你要用任何的方法 只要能讓你對他說：
"I'm over you."
「我不在乎你了」就行了
Over you.
不在乎你
That's what it is.
就是這個
Closure.
了結
Hello? Excuse me?
抱歉
Excuse me. Hel
抱歉…
-Hang on. -Excuse me?
請稍等 對不起啊
-What? -Hi. I'm sorry.
什麼？ 對不起
I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.
我需要跟你借一下電話
-I'm talking. -I see that.
我正在講耶 我看得出來
One phone call,I'll be very quick. I'll even pay for it myself.
我打一個電話就可以了 很快的，我甚至會付錢給你
You're being a little weird about your phone.
你對你的電話有點詭異耶
All right. Fine.
好…
I'll call you back.
我待會兒再打給你
Thank you.
謝了
Machine.
答錄機
-Just waiting for the beep. -Good.
我在等嗶嗶 太好了
Ross! Hi,it's Rachel.
羅斯，我是瑞秋
I'm just calling to say that...
我只是打來說…
...everything's fine.
…一切都很好
And I'm really happy for you...
我為你…
...and your cat.
…還有你的貓感到高興
Who,by the way,I think you should name Michael.
對了，我認為你應該叫他麥克
You see there, I'm thinking of names...
知道嗎？你瞧 我在想名字…
...so obviously I am over you.
…所以顯然我不在乎你了
I am over you.
我不在乎你了
And that,my friend, is what they call "closure."
這就是我那位朋友 所謂的「了結」
It's Sunday morning. I'm not running on a Sunday.
摩妮卡，今天是禮拜天早上 禮拜天我絕不跑步
-Why not? -Because it's Sunday!
為什麼？ 因為是禮拜天
It's God's day.
是神的日子
If you say stop,then we stop.
你說停我們就停
Stop.
停
No,come on! We can't stop!
不，別這樣啦，我們不能停
We got three more pounds to go!
還有三磅要減
I am the energy train and you are on board!
我是精力火車而你在車上
And how was the date?
你的約會怎麼樣啊？
I think there was a restaurant.
我記得有家餐廳
I know there was wine.
我還記得有酒
Actually,Julie's getting a cab.
事實上，茱莉在樓下叫計程車
I just need the cat toys. Did Monica say....
我想要拿貓玩具 摩妮卡有沒有說…
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
你為什麼那樣看我？
I'm sorry. I don't know,l....
對不起，我不知道…
I feel like I dreamed about you last night...
我覺得我昨晚好像夢到你…
... but I don't remember.
…但我不記得了
There they are.
在這兒
Did we speak on the phone? Did you call me?
我們昨晚有通電話嗎？ 你有沒有打給我？
No. I stayed at Julie's last night.
沒有，我昨晚住在茱莉那裡
I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?
事實上，我根本還沒回家呢 你介意我聽一下留言嗎？
Oh,yeah,go ahead.
請便啊
Rach,I got a message from you!
阿秋，我有你的留言
Who's Michael?
麥克是誰啊？
Oh,my God!
天啊
Ross,no! Hang up the phone. Give me the phone!
天啊，羅斯，把電話掛掉
Give me the
電話給我…
You're over me?
你不在乎我了
Oh,God!
天啊
-You're -Oh,God.
你… 我的天啊…
You're over me?
你不在乎我了？
When were you...
你是什麼時候…
... under me?
…在乎我的？
Rachel,do you...?
阿秋，你…？
I mean,were you?
我是說，你…你…？
What?
什麼？
Basically...
基本上…
...Iately,I've....
…最近我…
I've sort of had feelings for you.
我對你有一些感覺
You've had feelings for me?
你對我有感覺？
So? You had feelings for me first!
那又怎樣？你先對我有感覺的
You know about my You know I had
你知道我…
You know?
我是說，你知道我有…
Chandler told me.
錢德告訴我的
When did he? When did he? When did he?
錢德，他什麼時候，他…
When you were in China.
你在中國的時候
Meeting Julie.
認識茱莉時
Julie. That's Oh,God!
茱莉？茱莉？那… 天啊
I need to lie down.
我需要躺下來
No,I'm gonna stand.
不，你知道，我要站著
I'm gonna stand...
我要站著…
...and I'm gonna walk. I'm walking and I am standing.
…我要踱步 我踱步，而且我站著
Now you're over me?
現在你不在乎我了？
Are you over me?
你還在乎我嗎？
That's Julie.
那…那是茱莉
-Hi,Julie. -I've got a cab waiting.
茱莉 甜心，計程車在等喔
I'll be right down!
我馬上下來
Wait,so you're going?
等等，你要走了？
Well,okay,I have to. I can't deal with this right now.
對，我得走 我現在沒有辦法談這個
I mean,I've You know,I've got a cab.
計程車在等著
I've got a girlfriend. I'm gonna go get a cat.
我有女朋友 我要去領養一隻貓
Cat!
貓
-Hey,Joey. -Hey,Pheebs.
喬伊 菲比
How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?
你為什麼在看 猶太牧師彈電吉他？
I can't find the remote.
我找不到遙控器
Thank you.
謝謝
Scott asked me to come over for lunch and I did.
對了，史考約我去他家午餐 我去了
-And? -And we did.
然後… 我們做了
All right! Way to go!
正點，菲比好耶
Yea,me!
對呀
So how did it happen?
怎麼發生的？
I took your advice and asked him what was going on.
我聽了你的建議 問他到底怎麼回事啊？
What did he say?
那他說什麼？
He understands how sex can be a very emotional thing for a woman.
他瞭解性對女人而言呢 可以說是一件非常情緒化的事
And he was just afraid that I was going to get all:
他只是怕我會變得像…
"ls he gonna call me the next day?" and "Where is this going?"
「第二天是否會打電話給我」 「我們會有結局嗎」之類的
So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be serious.
所以他說他想等到 他準備開始認真了以後再說
So I said,"Okay. Relax,please."
所以我說「放輕鬆好嗎？」
Sex can be just about two people right there in the moment.
我是說，性可以只是 兩個人一時的感覺
If he wants to see me again,he can call. If not,that's fine too.
若他想再見我可以打電話給我 如果不想的話也沒關係
So after a lot of talking...
所以在長談之後…
... I convinced him.
…我說服他了
Let me get this straight.
讓我先搞清楚
He got you to beg to sleep with him.
他讓你求他跟你上床
He got you to say he never has to call you again.
他讓你說 他永遠不用再打電話給你
And he got you thinking this is a great idea?
而且還讓你覺得 這是一個好主意？
This man is my god!
我簡直崇拜他
I didn't get a cat.
我沒有領養貓
That's interesting.
真有趣
No,it's not "interesting." It's very,very not interesting.
不，那一點都沒有趣 那非常非常沒有趣
It's actually 100% the opposite of interesting.
事實上那百分之百是 有趣的相反，瑞秋
I got it,Ross.
好，我懂了，羅斯
You had no right to say you had feelings for me.
你沒有權利告訴我說 你曾經喜歡過我
I was doing great with Julie before I knew!
在我發現之前 我跟茱莉過得很快樂
I was doing great before I knew about you!
在我發現之前 我也過得很快樂
You think it's easy to see you with Julie?
你以為看你跟茱莉那樣 我心裡好受嗎？
You should've said something before!
你應該在我認識她之前說出來
I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything?
那時我不知道啊 那你為何從不說什麼呢？
There was never a good time.
因為總沒有機會
You only had a year. And we only hung out every night!
對，你有一年機會 我們每晚都在一起混
Not...
不是…
...every night.
…每個晚上
It's not like I didn't try. But things got in the way.
而且我也不是沒試過，瑞秋 但是每次都有事情發生
You know,like ltalian guys...
就像是意大利人啊…
...or ex-fiances...
…或者是前任的未婚夫啦…
...or ltalian guys.
…或者意大利人啊
There was one ltalian guy,okay? And do you have a point?
只有一個意大利人 你到底有沒有重點啊？
The point is,I don't need this right now!
重點是 我現在已經不需要這個了
Okay? It's too late.
太遲了
I'm with somebody else. I'm happy. This ship has sailed!
我在跟別人交往，我很快樂 這艘船開航了
You're just gonna put away your feelings for me?
你喜歡什麼時候擱開感情 都可以嗎？
I've done it since ninth grade. I'm good at it.
我從初三就開始這樣了 我早駕輕就熟了
All right,fine. You go ahead and do that.
那好，你儘管去做吧，羅斯
I don't need your ship!
我告訴你，我不需要你的蠢船
-Good. -Good!
好 好
And you know what? Now I got closure!
你知道嗎？我現在了結了
Try the bottom one.
試試下面那個
Monica,it's 6:30 in the morning.
摩妮卡，現在是早上六點半
We're not working out. It's over.
我們不再去運動，結束了
No way! With one pound to go? Come on!
怎麼啦？只剩一磅，來啦
We're workin',we're movin' We're in the zone,we're groovin'
我們運動，我們移動 我們在其中舞動
I don't mind the last pound.
我不在乎我的最後一磅
In fact,I kind of like the last pound.
我很喜歡這最後一磅
So don't make me do anything that I'll regret.
所以不要逼我 做下終生遺憾的事
What you gonna do,fat boy?
那你要做什麼，肥仔？
What?
什麼？
Nothing. Except tell you it's wonderful how much energy you have.
沒什麼，除了告訴你 我覺得你精力這麼充沛真棒
Well,thanks.
謝了
Especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.
尤其是你現在去找工作 找得焦頭爛額
You can't tell your parents you were fired,because they'd be disappointed.
你不能告訴你父母你被開除了 因為他們會非常的失望
It's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.
尤其你又沒有男朋友 可以借肩膀讓你哭
Well,no. But l....
沒有，但是我…
If it were me,I'd have difficulty getting out of bed at all.
我是說，如果是我的話 我想我會連起床都會很困難
You know,I try to stay positive.
我試著保持積極
So you....
那麼…
You feel like going for a run?
你想出去跑一跑嗎？
All right.
好吧
Because you don't have to. You could just take a nap right here.
你知道你不一定要去跑的 你可以在這裡睡一下